http://www.cee.org/privacy-policy

Skip to Content Skip to Navigation
Featured
Home
Contact
Search this site:
CEE’s 35th Anniversary Celebration
Programs & InitiativesResearch Science Institute (RSI)RSI Academic Program
Apply to RSI
Life at RSI
Alumni Honors
Global Community
USA Biolympiad (USABO)
STEM Activities & Labs Resource
CEE A&CWhat do we do?
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
CEE receives information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter or complete a requested form.
When registering or donating through Give Direct on our site, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information through Give Direct. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To process transactions
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of CEE thanking you for your donation.
To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for a donation will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your gift.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server through Give Direct. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) are not stored on our servers.
Do we use cookies?
We do not use cookies.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
Center for Excellence in Education
8201 Greensboro Drive, Suite 215
McLean, Virginia 22102
703-448-9062
www.cee.org
info@cee.org
CEE is a private, 501(c)(3) not-for-profit corporation that provides programs at no cost to its students selected to attend and teachers through collaborations with educational institutions, private foundations, corporations, government agencies, and individuals who share a commitment to educational excellence and leadership.
Connections
News & Announcements
Mon | November 23, 2020 | 9:40 AM
Applications Being Accepted for 2021 RSI at MIT
Fri | October 30, 2020 | 9:46 AM
CEE Program Alumnus Receives Prestigious Entrepreneur Award
Fri | October 23, 2020 | 4:03 PM
CEE Hosts Webinar on Taking a Drug from Idea to Market
Programs & InitiativesResearch Science Institute (RSI)RSI Academic Program
Apply to RSI
Life at RSI
Alumni Honors
Global Community
USA Biolympiad (USABO)
CEE A&CWhat do we do?
